{
    "id": "6f65acc91f4e453aa12fda97d3282002",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We went …………………………… in the morning.",
            "description": "There is no preposition in the expression go swimming, go walking, go climbing etc.",
            "answers": [
                "swimming",
                "for swimming",
                "to swimming"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s ……………………….. something.",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "to eat",
                "eat",
                "eating"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I went …………………….. Canada to meet my brother.",
            "description": "Use to to show direction. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She went dancing ……………………….. the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited all of my friends ……………………. my party.",
            "description": "You are invited to a specific event.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You .................... get some rest.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice.  ",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "had better",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my cousins ……………………… a singer.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after one of.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher had scarcely left the class ………………………. the children started talking.",
            "description": "Scarcely is followed by when or before.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "then",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had I opened the door, …………………….. the cat jumped out.",
            "description": "We use than after no sooner.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was hardly inside the house ……………………… it started raining.",
            "description": "Hardly is followed by when or before.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How about …………………….. a drink?",
            "description": "Use an ing form after how about and what about.",
            "answers": [
                "to have",
                "having"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She accused me ...................... stealing her watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}